watchmegrow.com 2006-11-09

# WatchMeGrow Childcare Internet Video Cameras & Online Viewing Systems

##### [Home](http://www.watchmegrow.com/index.shtml) 

##### [Sign Up](https://www.watchmegrow.com/signup.shtml) 

##### [Demonstration](http://www.watchmegrow.com/demonstration.shtml) 

##### [Childcare Providers](http://www.watchmegrow.com/childcareProviders.shtml) 

##### [Intergrators](http://www.watchmegrow.com/integrators.shtml) 

##### [Testimonials](http://www.watchmegrow.com/testimonials.shtml) 

##### [In the News](http://www.watchmegrow.com/inTheNews.shtml) 

##### [Contact Us](https://www.watchmegrow.com/contactUs.shtml) 

##### [Help](http://www.watchmegrow.com/help.shtml) 

**WatchMeGrow  
Quick Login **   
| 

|  |  This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [WatchMeGrow](http://www.watchmegrow.com/). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:   
  1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.   
  2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.   
  3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.   
  4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   
---|---  
  
|  We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.   
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.   
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.   
---|---  

|  We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.   
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.   
---|---  

#### We have greatly enjoyed the access WatchMeGrow provides to our child. Thank you!  
-Texas

#### I am a stay-at-home Mom with a business I run out of the home. I am on the computer all day and I really miss Jacob and I love to watch what he is doing at school. I really depend on this service.  
-Seattle, WA

**For more information,  
please click below...**   [](http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=1051208104212)
